
1[ { "id": 0, 
    "question": "An important difference between JSON and actual JavaScript objects is:", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "JSON attribute names should have quotation marks around them."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "JSON arrays should be surrounded in braces while JavaScript arrays use square brackets."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "JavaScript objects can be identified by a name, while JSON objects cannot be given a name."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "JavaScript does not surround numeric data (floating point) in quotation marks, while JSON requires this."} ]
  },
  
2  { "id": 1, 
    "question": "What does it mean when the readyState === 4 on an XMLHttpRequest object?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The server has finished processing the request and the response has been transmitted to the client."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The response from the server is currently being transmitted to the client."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "The open() method has been called but the request has not yet been sent to the server."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The open() method has not yet been called, although the XMLHttpRequest object has been created."} ]
  },
  
3  { "id": 2, 
    "question": "An XMLHttpRequest sends a GET request and now has status === 200. What does this mean?", 
	"correctAnswer": "c", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter": "a", "value": "The request was valid but the client is not allowed to access the resource"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The requested resource could not be found."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "The requested resource was returned successful."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "The client has sent too many requests in a certain amount of time."} ]
  },
  
4  { "id": 3, 
    "question": "When should the callback function for an AJAX request be invoked?", 
	"correctAnswer": "c", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "When the page has finished loading"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "When the user refreshes the page"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "When the readyState property for the request changes"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "none of the above"} ]
  },

5  { "id": 4, 
    "question": "How can the properties of a JSON object be accessed in JavaScript?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "Iterating over the properties of the object. Eg. for(x in myObj)..."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "Using dot notation Eg. myObj.biz"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Using bracket notation Eg. myObj[\"biz\"]" },
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "All of the above."} ]
  },
  
6  { "id": 5, 
    "question": "Why exactly is AJAX \"asynchronous\"? ", 
	"correctAnswer": "c", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "The user must always wait for the request to finish processing, although the page is not reloaded."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The page is reloaded while pages in other browser tags are unaffected."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "The data is retrieved from the server without reloading the page."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "None of the above"} ]
  },
  
7  { "id": 6, 
    "question": "How can the objects in a JSON array be processed together?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "Using the attribute names of the first attribute in each object"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "Using a for loop with bracket notation with an index value for the object "},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Using the for-each function loop with the element passed to the inner function"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "Both B and C"} ]
  },
  
8  { "id": 7, 
    "question": "What type of data is contained in the responseText property of an XMLHttpRequest?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "A String containing the requested data (a DOMString)"},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "A String which describes the current status of the request"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "A string describing the readyState of the request"},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "A user-friendly text version of the response status"} ]
  },
  
9  { "id": 8, 
    "question": "Why is it usually not recommended to pass a value of false as the third argument in the open() method of XMLHttpRequest (use a synchronous request)?", 
	"correctAnswer": "d", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "Because the function returns immediately, which means that an event listener must be used."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "The server may become overwhelmed with requests"},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "Data may be lost when the response is received."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "It leads to poor performance since the function blocks until it returns."} ]
  },
  
10  { "id": 9, 
    "question": "Which statement best describes thee main advantages of JSON over XML?", 
	"correctAnswer": "a", 
    "answers" : [ {"letter":"a", "value": "JSON is lightweight and uses a simpler syntax which is easier to use in JavaScript, requiring less bandwidth to transfer data."},
		           {"letter": "b", "value": "JSON uses schemas to define data types and the data structure, allowing data to be validated."},
				   {"letter": "c", "value": "JSON is supported in many different programming languages, especially JavaScript, while XML is only supported in a few languages."},
				   {"letter": "d", "value": "JSON files tend to be larger than the equivalent XML, given that the file headers contain a significantly more metadata."} ]
  }
  
 ]
				   